so
and I'm wearing of it holding
this is Shalon concrete you saw an
Indian plate they tend to be bigger
you have to be gentle because they're
not very scales are sort of heads
so what happens with this money but
there is an anti-venom but it can cause
organ damage even if even if you get
anti-venom so you don't really want to
be bitten lips
oh it is beautiful that is cracker
outside of my fence mmm I don't want you
to get well into the dogs or gets
injured by the dogs so I go must buy a
crate and it really stinks
it's worse than a rat snake
watch out for more crazy
it's still actually really bad so now
you washed your hands with it so Chloe's
just smells like smells like inside
feces that is the strongest
yeah that's signal is bad this is quite
potent you often wouldn't necessarily
even feel the bite on the plate with the
teeth were actually like maybe a
millimeter or so tiny buckle is it yeah
yeah I think so actually
I think those leaders might have bigger
teeth then creates fangs it's a
neurotoxin you stop breathing and your
organs start shutting down